The perfect love story. Until it became the perfect crime.
All Good Things is a mystery, thriller, romance film directed by Andrew Jarecki.
Newly-discovered facts, court records and speculation are used to elaborate the true love story
and murder mystery of the most notorious unsolved murder case in New York history.
David Marks, played by Ryan Gosling.
Katie Marks, played by Kirsten Dunst.
Sanford Marks, played by Frank Langella.
Deborah Lehrman, played by Lily Rabe.
Malvern Bump, played by Philip Baker Hall.
Daniel Marks, played by Michael Esper.
All Good Things is a 2010 American mystery/crime romantic drama film directed by
Andrew Jarecki and written by Marcus Hinchey and Marc Smerling.
Inspired by the life of Robert Durst, it stars Ryan
Gosling, Kirsten Dunst, and Frank Langella.
Gosling portrays the wealthy son of a New York real estate tycoon (Langella) who develops a disturbing relationship with
his wife (Dunst) and becomes suspected of a series of murders, as well as his wife's unsolved disappearance.
All Good Things was filmed between April and July
2008 in Connecticut and New York.
Originally scheduled for a July 24, 2009 release, the film
ultimately received a limited release on December 3, 2010.
Durst professed admiration for the film, and after previously not
cooperating with journalists, offered to be interviewed by Jarecki.
Durst would ultimately sit with Jarecki for more than 20 hours over a multi-year
period, which led to the true crime documentary series The Jinx in 2015.
The film explores themes of difficult childhood, patriarch,
childhood trauma, dysfunctional marriage.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and emotional.